electrically hopefully I've got those
words right because of a man but what
they're doing is using your normal
frequencies in the car now
they sell two boxes one is for computers
one is for points it condenses
apparently the ones for points and
condensers work for cars you can't put
him onto a computer car you can't
interchange and once the computer cars
you can go and take them off there and
put them back two points ecumenical and
those are us oxidization things are for
removing the rust on your vehicles you
know oxidization on your bumper body
aluminium your wheels your phone and
carry and so on like don't you mercy
while they are rust removers okay so
that's a frequency that they're driving
into their to remove that but it keeps
your cargo tip brushed oxidized it
wouldn't be much good for you if it was
stopping you go with it because you'd
have a car now why would entrust but
wouldn't go so and they've used a
different frequency for doing that as
well does how all the information within
this alright so the the thing is what I
found is the DC Magneto's actually made
motors run without all the rest of the
gear then they come up into a magneto
that call today for that big neato can
also have points condensers can have a
spark web bite you see the original
diesel magneto didn't kick flat line
your other ones never got to be
converted because that that kind of
spark what bites you don't run cars and
you say well I grabbed a spark plug
leads and everything else off a coil in
the car and it bites me more fewer use
guys out there if you want to try it and
I've just shown a few people here and
they got bitten for a long time at first
but there are ways to grab hold of that
spark at the end of any spark plug lead
and not get the same spot
and not get bit okay
you got any idea how many people are
going to be booted all over the country
so I don't experiment with this with
that
I just went out getting Buddhists right
I just grabbed it and I'm busy
I'll tell you how it's done I'll let you
think about it for a minute but I want
you to play get better Daffy you times
if you like but to closer you get the
place you think I'm not going right so
is it your right hand or left hand Joe
French won't make any difference
my closer you get to that lead and make
the spark jump oh there's a little tree
don't bread the lead you're gonna get
booted and don't be too far away you're
gonna get booted Gary's a happy little
closing but like the citizen you know
they smoke pot and your point there is a
point Jack that spark can go to you and
will not bite you which means it's not
what you might call an AC it's not
anyone I see able to kick over the kill
right DC don't kick don't kill and not
post I'm not doing that right but is
also every action there's an opposite
nickel you can have something which is
jumping and it's still flat line and I
know about that too well here don't my
bike and that's what you can find it any
spark plug lead okay any coil anything
else that you want to get bitten now
what I found is Ted you have a stylo
miter and a Stottlemeyer is a generator
a generator outputs electricity and a
starter maybe you throw electricity at
and a generator for Ted not alternating
current Rosetta will be called an
alternator in a generator is the the
electricity coming out of a generator
the way they do it with the brushes and
sharps and everything else also has to
be regulated for what nice to be
regulated in a lot has it got to be
regulated for the wipers okay keep going
it's got a redraw all of those all of
the ability but does it what the lights
of our fusible link something that's all
you're telling an ear you're asking boy
am i prepare hope you can ask the
question ha ha ha well see I know when
to shut up
sorry go in today so this generator
actually put out a DC generation on
field so if you grab the generator do
you get kit like an maybe an automating
okay well the generator has to be
regulated but will a generator of any
frequency at all actually because the
your spark out of your coil and
everything else has to be taken back to
DC flatline that's what happens before
in your engine will fire because they
see it won't fire okay it has to be
equalized
equalized that's why when you see on the
spark coming out to your spark plugs on
the Commodore in any other car if you on
the chequered it's not positive or
negative because it goes to both the
positive and the negative it's attracted
to on
on your battery so it has to be
something else okay so what I found in
the Suzuki and went back to that and
everything else is and your starter
motor is a is a generator and the
generators of starter motor
so they got machines out there that you
use for starting and then your press
apartment and then they generate
electricity so they'll do both in the
two same device same little they go so
what I've done is I didn't pull the
starter motor in I didn't all did the
starter motor I didn't do anything else
I changed that fractional field going to
the star mode am I going too funny Lutz
I mean ain't you feel going to the
starter motor so the starter motor if
you took power out of the starter motor
would it actually run an engine would it
be the right say spark to put to a spot
local you ask the stupid question him
course not why because movie star Nevada
doesn't have a jumping spot so a
generator is it can you take the wire
off a generator and put straight to a
spark plug and run your engine and then
think so so can you do it from an
alternator because it definitely pulses
the same no all right so it's got it
wrong frequency I'll use the